<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Authors on Behzad Nouri</title><link>https://b-nouri.github.io/authors/</link><description>Recent content in Authors on Behzad Nouri</description><generator>Source Themes academia (https://sourcethemes.com/academic/)</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright &amp;copy; {year}</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://b-nouri.github.io/authors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://b-nouri.github.io/authors/admin/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://b-nouri.github.io/authors/admin/</guid><description>&lt;p>The passion for programming and designing new software tools made me change my field and follow a masters in IT. Since then, I have been inovelved in numerious IT projects as business analyst, lead product manager, project manager and data scientist.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Having &lt;strong>more than 7 years&lt;/strong> of industry experience, I have learned a lot about data modelling and database design, Sofware project management, data warehousing, BI and reporting systems.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>My first interaction with data science and it&amp;rsquo;s toolset roots back in &lt;strong>2013&lt;/strong> when I used &lt;strong>R Language&lt;/strong> for discovering the trend of AI reserach employing text mining algorithms.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As I have always been a passionate learner, I decided to dive deeper in machine learning and AI and started a new program in data science in 2019. Since that time I have done various projects in statistical modelling, machine learning and big data analytics.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>In my current day to day job at CLdN I use &lt;strong>python&lt;/strong>, &lt;strong>SQL&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>Power BI&lt;/strong> a lot. Ocasionally, based on the nature of the project I may decide to employ &lt;strong>R&lt;/strong>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Robert Ford</title><link>https://b-nouri.github.io/authors/robert-ford/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://b-nouri.github.io/authors/robert-ford/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>